What a surprise to have A-Man and his two friends here today!
Yay!
It's very rare to have them on my channel.
I don't have an image of them being guests on my channel.
I don't have much of an image of them as guests on my channel, and I can't really say anything about it.
I'm glad that we have the same office.
I was on location once.
How did you do on location?
Did you get any feedback?
There was one woman who was a big fan of A-MAST and even came to shake hands with me.
She even came to the handshake session. She sent me T-shirts and other things to the theater, and she was very happy about the location shooting,
I'm also keeping this YouTube thing today a secret from the handshake, like, actually.
The people who collaborate with me are also sitting down.
They're watching.
I'm going to fall over.
I'm pussyfooting around.
I'll introduce them in real life.
Sometimes it's the same with idols, but even comedians like A-MAST and who they like,
Like there are two favorites.
If they are in somewhat similar circles, I think it's fair enough, but when it comes to who is doing who with whom,
I don't know why they do that.
I totally understand.
I like A-MAST and Westland.
Why not?
It's one or the other, usually.
Is there someone with a common pattern?
If it's a common pattern, there's Maki, the heroine of Sanji, or Picolohee,
Or a female comedian who calls herself "Gah,
A female comedian who calls herself "Gah.
She calls herself "Gah".
It's not a pull.
If I had to choose between offense and defense, I like female comedians who play offense.
That's true.
That's why none of the people who like us like Borjuk.
She is not a comedian that makes everyone happy.
Who do people who like Yukilin like in terms of Yukilin?
Like Nikoyag.
Idols who are much younger than me.
I've been around for a long time, but I still like idols, so I'm always looking at new idols.
It's not AKB.
Within AKB, it's probably impossible to find someone who likes me.
How do you say it?
Impossible!
The people who have liked me for a long time don't go to the younger generation anymore.
That's what I mean.
They don't love me.
The fans who like young people don't like me, and the people who like me don't like young people.
And those who like me don't like young people.
This is very common.
But I've already done a lot of things.
Producing cosmetics.
That's right.
Here comes businessman Yubayashi.
Today, I did her makeup with Yubayashi cosmetics.
And the sweet makeup really suits you.
I don't wear pink makeup very often, but it's really nice.
It really blends in.
It looks good on you.
Me?
You should see it.
Even Mr. Parfait is on the short list.
Keep talking.
What do you enjoy and what do you not like?
Everyone's asking.
What kind of work do you do?
Well, it's pretty much the same thing on YouTube.
I'm pretty much free to do what I want.
That's the main thing.
No strings attached.
There's no group activities.
I think that's tough.
It's pretty common.
When a woman who's an interesting variety entertainer
There's nothing to do when you're playing to the masses.
There's nothing obvious.
It's very funny.
I don't need comedy so much
When lightheartedness seems to be the market principle
I can't do anything.
I understand that.
But when I'm in a variety show with a lot of people
When there are kids younger than you on the hill
I'm just an ordinary nice girl in the gap.
There's a variety.
You told me before that you have a lot of regrets.
That's right.
The older students don't love me.
They don't love me.
Smooch.
Stroked.
I'm scared.
If she's cute, she's cute...
I think she's cute.
You work at the same office, don't you?
Who do you get along with?
She said she'd take me to see my mom.
I hate to say it, but...
She's like Sunshine Ikezaki.About Sunshine Ikezaki
Mr. Ikezaki's Private Bali or so.
Um, let's go out to eat.
How's it going lately?
How do you drink, Myan?
How do you drink, Miyan?
Who do you name when asked who's young in AKB?
I'm the general manager of AKB, and I'm young,
Well, she is about six years older than me,
I'm in my 3rd term and she's in her 15th,
So I was very considerate of her and drank with her at dinner,
I feel like I have to take care of her.
Do you give advice?
No, I don't give advice anymore.
My enthusiasm and the young people's enthusiasm are probably different,
They probably don't need my advice either.
I'm even breathing a little bit.
Do you want my advice? Advice.
Well, which is it?
I don't really know what you're asking me about.
I don't know. It's so different.
If you're an idol or something, you might want to use a method,
I mean, if you're an idol, you might have a method or something that you should do, but if you're a comedian
But with comedians, it's the opposite,
Even if you're a bad guy, there's a chance you'll make money from it.
Fix it!
But it's hard to be an idol, too.
Young girls like 17th and 18th term recently
I was shaking hands with them and they were doing so much.
When I was shaking hands with a young girl who was in her 17th or 18th term, she said, "I'm in my 17th or 18th term.
When I was shaking hands with a young girl who was in her 17th or 18th term, she said, "You're all talking to me like I'm an old man.
But it's not something I'm prepared to do.
Thank you for the older fans.
But I can't do that anymore.
You're right.
I'm sure you're happy.
I hope it makes your fans happy, too.
It's a new kind of friendship.
You're right. I'm not going to tell them.
What are you up to? Hongo...
Certainly.
I really don't have any.
If I had one of these, I'd give out a lot of them.
But I haven't had any so far.
I can say that...
I've been doing a lot of work behind the scenes.
In the stock market.
At the MXs, right?
You haven't been doing any of that, have you?
Are you thinking straight?
No, I'm not.
I'm not thinking about it. I'm letting him think about it.
Double it.
If I were to look at one goal other than one year, what would it be?
A year?
A regular part of the duo.
Certainly.
And YouTube.
Maybe 200,000, 300,000 people.
And I'm talking about a year.
But YouTube is really
If you only think about the next video and the next and the next
I don't want to think about the universe.
What? How long are we going to do this for? I don't know.
Where is YouTube going?
How old am I going to be?
How long am I going to be on YouTube before I'm too old?
I know, I know, I know.
I'd be dead if I had to face it.
Let's just take it easy.
Oh, come on.
We're not there yet.
I need some killer content.
At least this one for now.
The comment stuff has to be killer.
The comment stuff is, but...
Slowly something in me is falling apart.
I want Yukirin to come over here once.
Let's have her listen to our anti-commentary
Yukirin to listen to our anti-comments.
I was thinking about that at first.
That's a little...
We can't expose Yukirin to our anti-comments.
Yukirin's fans
It's a little bit more angled.
It's 10 times more annoying.
It's not that they're annoying.
It's annoying.
And what's more...
What? You know what?
Lately, it's been a little better.
It's like, "I'm not going to stop you.
Are you doing okay? Pretty good.
Are you doing it?
What?
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
It seems like a good fit.
It's my place.
It's still difficult.
You'll cry.You'll cry.
After one...
There are more than a few people who would love to.
People who want you to pick them up.
That's true.
I just don't think it'll get rid of them.
I'm sure it won't.
Are you turning it off?
I'm turning it off.
What? You can turn it off.
Let's do it.
I didn't know you could delete comments.
Let's turn off the sensitivity.
Should I turn it off?
And the bans, you can put in keywords or something.
Like a ban code.
Oh! You can do that?
I'm just saying, you're doing a great job.
Destroyer noticed.
I noticed that the manager talks a lot!
Video.
No, no, no, not at all.
Smile at the manager.
"Sit down!
Smile.
See you often, see you anytime.
Thank you very much.
I'm also a massager, and I'd like to say hello to you, and I'm so happy to be able to do this for the first time.
I'm doing what I love the most, and this is the first time I'm doing it at the Masser.
Please come to the Masser's and see the battle.
I'm not sure if I should say this, but I had a lot of fun at the Grand Arrival, so please come and check it out too.
I'm going to go take a look at the anti-commentary.
Well then, thank you very much for coming to the show.
Please follow us!